## Márk Munkácsi

From: Budapest, Hungary Currently: Dubai, UAE

markmunkacsi@protonmail.com codermark.dev github.com/munkacsimark

## senior frontend developer

**Profile** 

I'm a **frontend developer** with ~8 years of experience. Mainly I'm building performant client side apps designed for humans with modern JavaScript tools like **React**, **Vue** or **Svelte**. Or just write plain **JavaScript** or **Typescript** code. I also started to learn **Solidity** but I have no real experience with it for now.

**Experience** 

SideShift.ai, Remote – Aug. 2021 - Aug. 2022

SideShift is a crypto exchange. My responsibility was improving client side architecture and performance. Also implementing **end-to-end tests** from scratch. Our stack was **React** with **Typescript, GraphQL** and **nodejs** on server side. Also worked on some **CI** task improvements and touched **backend** code too.

Coinweb.io, Remote - May 2020 - Jul. 2021

I worked mostly with **React** on our **blockchain wallet** but also wrote some **React Native** and **nodejs** code as well.

Docler Holding, Budapest - Oct. 2019 - May 2020

At Docler I worked on a **desktop application**'s frontend. The app was written in C++ and QT, with an embedded browser view. We used **React** for UI and **Redux-Saga** to manage state handling of the application.

Ingatlan.com, Budapest - July 2018 - Sept. 2019

Ingatlan.com is Hungary's bigest real estate site. Our team worked on the main site. We maintained a **huge legacy codebase** and turned it into a component based **responsive UI** using **Vue** framework. We used and developed our own **component library** and **design system** closely with the design team.

Skawa Innovation, Budapest - Sept. 2014 - June 2018

I worked on client side of our main project, Easyling. The app is a widely used online proxy translation tool. Our app and its components were written in **Angular 1**, later we started to migrate it to **Angular 2** using **Dart** instead of Typescript.

**Education** 

**Web developer** - Athéné SZKI., Budapest – 2012 - 2014 **Graphic designer** - Athéné SZKI., Budapest – 2009 - 2011

**Skills** 

As a professional I like to work with **new technologies**. My strengths are mostly the web and the client side, but I'm interested to dive deeper into backend as well. I'm comfortable to work on **high-traffic** websites/web apps.